http://www.schoolspecialty.com/privacy-statement

Message Dialog
Close
Display Update Message
Product Comparison
The maximum number of products that can be compared is 4. Please refine your selection.
OK
Your session is about to timeout due to inactivity.
Click OK to extend your time for an additional 0 minutes.
OK
This item has been successfully added to your list.
Current Order
This item has been successfully added:
Model Classrooms
Due to COVID-19, orders may be temporarily delayed. Read our COVID-19 Safety Protocol Pledge to You
Privacy Statement
By accessing this website ("Website"), you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use this Website. School Specialty, LLC (hereafter "School Specialty") shares your concerns regarding the privacy of personal information collected on the Internet. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of School Specialty in connection with its Website. If you feel that School Specialty is not abiding by its posted Privacy Policy, you should contact School Specialty by email at
iscp@schoolspecialty.com
.
Information Collection and Use
School Specialty is the owner of the information collected on this Website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Policy. School Specialty collects information from our users at several different points on our Website. We use your information to facilitate the services we provide you in the sale and distribution of products and services that you request. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Website, to troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems. You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Website usage, improve our content and product offerings, solve technical problems and customize our Website's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our Website and better tailor the Website to meet your needs. School Specialty reserves all rights and exemptions under applicable privacy legislation.
User ID and Password
You are responsible for all actions taken with your Username and Password, including fees or expenses related to its misuse. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your School Specialty Username or Password to any third party, with whom you do not wish to be completely liable for their actions. If you choose to share your Username and Password or other information with a third party, you are responsible for all actions taken with your Username and Password. If you lose control of your Password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your Password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your Password and notify us by email at
websupport@schoolspecialty.com
.
Information from Other Sources
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Website. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Website, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Website as well as having the ability to take advantage of all of the features of our Website. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Website. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
Log Files
We also collect non-personally identifiable information through our Internet log files, which record data such as IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of the Website. This information may be used to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to monitor the Website's use, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to personally identifiable information for these and other purposes such as personalizing your experience on the Website and evaluating our Internet systems.
Sharing
We will share aggregate demographic information with our suppliers and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual user.
We and our suppliers may use outside parties for the purposes of providing online registration, ticketing and payment services, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They might have access to personal information needed to perform their functions.
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy business operations or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that School Specialty or substantially all of its assets or shares are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our Terms of Use, or protect the rights, property, or safety of School Specialty, our users, or others. We do share such information on a need to know basis with shippers and credit companies when applicable. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
School Specialty gives you access to user information regarding you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. When you update information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase, enter a contest, register for an event, or to take advantage of certain School Specialty features.
Contests
If you enter a contest or register for an event, we will generally ask you to provide certain information (such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, and/or photograph). Do not submit information that you do not want School Specialty to access or use. School Specialty may use personally identifiable information submitted in connection with a contest or special event to provide information and services to Website users and to allow School Specialty to: (i) promote and support School Specialty's products and services and our subsidiaries' products and services; (ii) contact you; and/or (iii) announce contest winners on our Website, our subsidiaries' websites, or through our marketing materials.
Links
This Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that School Specialty is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Website.
Security
This Website takes reasonable precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our Website asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted. While we use encryption to protect most sensitive information online, we also seek to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a Customer Service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you have any questions about the security at our Website, you can send an email to
iscp@schoolspecialty.com
.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by email to
websupport@schoolspecialty.com
.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the facility to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our Website. For example, e-mail correspondence from us has an 'opt-out' option so users who receive correspondence from us can remove their email address off of our lists.
Minors
SSI intends this Website for use only by individuals who are 18 years of age or older (or such other age of majority as may apply in your state or province of residency), or by minors with the consent of their parent or guardian. Please do not use the Website without the consent of your parent or guardian if you are not at least 18 years of age (or such other age of majority as may apply in your state or province of residency). We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. You can use the Website and view content without any personal information being collected. If you are required to enter a username, we encourage you to make up your user name, rather than use your real name. If you are under the age of 13, please register anonymously.
Privacy Officer
School Specialty has appointed a Privacy Officer to address issues related to this Privacy Policy. Inquiries to the Privacy Officer should be directed to:
E-mail:
iscp@schoolspecialty.com
Fax: 920-882-5603
Postal address:
School Specialty
Attn: Privacy Officer
PO Box 1579
Appleton, WI 54912
Access to Information
You may request access to your personal information and particulars as to how your personal information is being used or disclosed. Such requests should be made in writing to the following postal address:
School Specialty
Attn: Privacy Officer
PO Box 1579
Appleton, WI 54912
School Specialty will respond to such requests as required by applicable privacy legislation within the time limits required by applicable privacy legislation. School Specialty reserves the right to apply or seek any extensions available under applicable legislation.
School Specialty reserves the right to refuse access to information where applicable legislation permits or requires. You have the right to appeal to any government official with jurisdiction to hear appeals from refusals to provide access to your information.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to modify our Privacy Policy, we will post those modifications on our Website so our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. Your use of this Website following any such modification constitutes your agreement to the modified Policy. For this reason, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website.
